Finding Aids to Personal Papers and Special Collections in the VMFA Archives Lillian Thomas Pratt Personal Papers, 1901-1947 SC-07
VMFA Archives, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts
- Series 1: Schaffer Collection, 1934-1947, undated; SC-07-01
  - Series 1.5: Item Descriptions, 1934-1945, undated; SC-07-01.5
    - 888, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 893, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 894, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 901, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 905, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 907, 908, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 909, 904, 911, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 912, Sep. 30, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1017, Oct. 29, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1041, Oct. 29, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1049, Oct. 29, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 92, Feb. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 972, Feb. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 982, Feb. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1006, Feb. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1043, Feb. 17, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1176, Mar. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 37, Apr. 2, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 991, Apr. 2, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1088, Apr. 2, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1097, Apr. 2, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1179, Apr. 2, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1306, Apr. 2, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 476, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 478, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 482, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 537, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 986, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 987, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1035, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1166, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1189, Apr. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 804, Apr. 11, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1291, Apr. 11, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 980, May 18, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1085, May 18, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 533, May 20, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 533 Duplicate, May 20, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 535, May 20, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 535 Duplicate, May 20, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 539, July 28, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1101, July 28, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 509, Aug. 26, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 997, Aug. 26, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 477, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 479, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 480, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 481, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 536, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 538, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 665, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 989, Oct. 29, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 75, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 93, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 906, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1073, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1075, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1078, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1182, 1183, 778, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1315, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1350, Dec. 1, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 5)
    - 1343, Jan. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1364, Jan. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1367, Jan. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1464, Mar. 19, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1537, Mar. 19, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1546, Mar. 19, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1578, Mar. 19, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1556, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1573, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1576, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1580, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1661, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1736, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1737, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2237, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2238, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G-3, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G-5, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G-8, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G-13, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G-14, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G-16, Aug. 18, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1509, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1568, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1591, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1934, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1956, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2136, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2243, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G-22, Oct. 1, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 798, Oct.11, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1205, Oct.11, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2443, Nov. 1945 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2891, Nov. 1945 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 181, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 540, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 598, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1022, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1044, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1291, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1326, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1479, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1524, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1543, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1569, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1735, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1749, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 1763/2723, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2122, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2247, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2278, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2279, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2281, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2297, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2299, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2300, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2322, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2323, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2325, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2326, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2340, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2353, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2373, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2376, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2419, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2421, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2445, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2453, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2454, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2455, 2456, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2457, 2461, 2467, 2474, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2460, 2465, 2470, 2472, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2464, 2468, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2496, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2497, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2498, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2512, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2524, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2525, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2568, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2651, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2657, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2675, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2680, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2691, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2692, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2722, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2786, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2821, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2859, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2868, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2869, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2870, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2881, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - 2882, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - JZ-1, JZ-2, JZ-3, JZ-4, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - L-14, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - G.25, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
    - Gold presentation box of Nicholas II of Russia, undated (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 6)
- Series 2: Hammer Galleries, 1933-1945, undated; SC-07-02
  Box 1 (5 Folders, 1 Oversize Item and 1 Binder): This series is comprised of invoices, price tags, item descriptions, exhibition labels and correspondence that document the purchases Pratt made from the Hammer Galleries in the 1930s and 1940s. The Lord and Taylor invoices are undated, but the item numbers match up with Hammer Galleries price tags, and the Galleries did present and sell their collection at Lord and Taylor in the early 1930s (probably 1934 based upon letterhead from the item descriptions).
  Price tags were often annotated with price reductions or alterations in the item’s description. Item descriptions are extremely detailed, and include the item number and the date purchased. Most of the item descriptions were annotated by museum staff at some point with VMFA accession numbers. A note in Pratt’s hand is written on the item description for a traveling clock (item number 5253, purchased June 16, 1933) and says “Given to H.R.H. Princess Margaret Rose of England May 1939.” She received a letter of acknowledgment and appreciation back from Lady Constance Harriet Stuart Gaskell, a Woman of the Bedchamber to Queen Mary.
  Finally, the few exhibition labels were used in the Hammer Collection’s “Russian Imperial Exhibit” at Lord and Taylor. Four are still mounted on the original gold colored panels.
  The series is divided into five subseries: Series 2.1: Lord and Taylor Invoices, [1933]; Series 2.2: Price Tags, n.d.; Series 2.3: Item Descriptions, 1933-1945, n.d.; Series 2.4: Exhibition Labels, 1933-1934, n.d.; Series 2.5: Correspondence, 1939.
  - Series 2.1: Lord and Taylor Invoices, [1933]; SC-07-02.1
    - Ikon 5278, Ikon 5282, Ikon 5283, Ikon 5279, Ikon 5277, Jan. 27, [1933] (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 7)
    - Ikon 5281, Ikon 5280, Ikon 5286, Ikon 5284, Jan. 27, [1933] (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 7)
    - 5278, 5282, 5259, 5284, 5279, Feb. 1, [1933] (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 7)
    - 5283, 5281, 5286, 5280, Feb. 1, [1933] (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 7)
    - Icon D 1000, Icon 4580, Feb. 17, [1933] (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 7)
    - Cope X 896, Ikon 5232, Feb. 23, [1933] (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 7)
  - Series 2.2: Price Tags, undated; SC-07-02.2
    - E-43, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - A-104, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - A-105, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - D-1000, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - H-3825, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - H-4098, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 4108, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - X-4110, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 4122-C, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 4404, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 4580 (2 tags attached together), undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 4809, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 4809, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 4830, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5054, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5253, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5253, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5259, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5358, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5523, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5524, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5524, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 5846, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - X-6101, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 6577, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - X-6787, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - X-6794, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - 10685-B, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
    - Icon A68, Icon, Icon, H3825, Cheese Scoop, Icon A105, Icon 5846, Snuffbox 6577, undated (Binder SC-07 Binder 1)
  - Series 2.3: Item Descriptions, 1933-1945, undated; SC-07-02.3
    - X 4110, Jan. 25, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - F 99 D, Jan. 25, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - F 99 C, Jan. 25, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - H 4098, Jan. 26, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5054, Jan. 26, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5358, Jan. 26, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - H 4108, Jan. 26, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4809, Jan. 26, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - X 6101, Jan. 27, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4830, Jan. 27, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4809, Jan. 27, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 10685-B, Feb. 1, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5253, Feb. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5259, Feb. 14, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - D 1000, Feb. 17, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4580, Feb. 17, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5253, June 16, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 3550, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 3623, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - F43, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - X 6154, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4404, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - X 5153, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - X 5096, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - X 6396, Oct. 2, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 6025, Oct. 31, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - E-1000, Oct. 31, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 6787, Dec. 4, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - X 6707, Dec. 4, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - X 6794, Dec. 4, 1933 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4763, Jan. 4, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5528, Jan. 4, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 6136, Jan. 4, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4765, Jan. 4, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 6111, Feb. 1, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 6019, Feb. 1, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 6148, Feb. 1, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5421, Mar. 26, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5538, Mar. 26, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4122 C, May 3, 1934 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - E-313, Jan. 31, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - A-104, Jan. 31, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5547, June 21, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5401, June 21, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5687, June 21, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - A-62, June 21, 1935 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5570, Mar. 6, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - Easter Egg, Easter [Apr. 12], 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - AS-1312, May, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - E-327, May, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - E-451, Aug. 17, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - GT-1530/3, Nov. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - GT-1530/2, Nov. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - E-762/80, Nov. 9, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 4776, Nov. 12, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - E-43, Nov. 12, 1936 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - IP-1553/2, Jan. 29, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - ME-1249, Feb. 8, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - 5571, May 11, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - JJ-5050/2, Oct. 2, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - AV-5008/1, Oct. 2, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - RB-5210/37, Dec., 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - RH-1815, Dec. 9, 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - E-517/4, Christmas [Dec. 25], 1937 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
    - IP-1843/4, Jan. 8, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/4, Jan. 27, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - A-61, Jan. 27, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - E-754, Jan. 27, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/3, Jan. 27, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/1, Jan. 28, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/47, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/41, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/46, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/39, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/45, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/38, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/33, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/32, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/44, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/9, Feb. 1, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5214/13, Feb. 2, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5209/26, Apr. 15, 1938 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5380-13, Jan. 9, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5380/2, Jan. 31, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5408/10, Jan. 31, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - VD-5399/16, Feb. 4, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5408/17, Feb. 4, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5416/29, Feb. 17, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - CA-5364/2, Feb. 17, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5380/3, Feb. 17, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5332/7, Feb. 17, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5389/2, Feb. 17, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5416/28, Feb. 20, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5380/16, Feb. 23, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5380/11, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5413/4, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5408/5, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5380/14, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5408/12, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5408/11, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5413/3, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5380/10, Feb. 24, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - VD-5399/5, Mar. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - VD-5399/4, Mar. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5408/16, Mar. 3, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-845/1, Mar. 15, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - 3531, Mar. 17, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5454/3, Apr. 19, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - 5448, Apr. 19, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-1842/12, Apr. 19, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - 5449, Apr. 19, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-1842/8, Apr. 19, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - RH-5409/25, June 1, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Rooster, Sep. 25, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Jade Coupe, Sep. 25, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Bear Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Bear Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Vase, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Easter Egg Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Easter Egg Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Easter Egg Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Easter Egg Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Easter Egg Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Easter Egg Charm, Oct. 2, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Silver Vase, Dec. 4, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Ink Well, Dec. 4, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Locket, Dec. 6, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Parasol Handle, Dec. 6, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Parasol Handle, Dec. 6, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - Bulldog, Dec. 6, 1939 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
    - 5450-6, Jan. 5, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5625-11, Jan. 5, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - E23, Jan. 5, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5550-1, Jan. 5, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - RH1698-100, Jan. 9, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5509, Jan. 9, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - RH5380-6, Jan. 9, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - RH5380-2, Jan. 9, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - RH5380-9, Jan. 9, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - RH5413-2, Jan. 9, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - RH5408-14, Jan. 9, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5478-5, Jan. 10, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5625-3, Jan. 24, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5450-17, Jan. 31, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - RH-5332-17, Feb. 6, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5756-19, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5903-4, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5903-3, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5777-8, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5839-12, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5839-9, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5840-6, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5808-1, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5756-18, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5791-10, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5903-1, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5903-5, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5903-6, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 6201-1, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 5870-3, Dec. 4, 1940 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 1189-8, Jan., 1941 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - 505-6, Feb., 1941 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)
    - Miniature in Frame, Feb. 26, 1941 (Box SC-07 Box 1, Folder Folder 10)